

✓ sadra.khanjari@gmail.com

+98 910 116 9066

Iran/Tehran Timezone

sk2ip.github.io

in sadra-khanjari

SK2iP

EDUCATION

BSc in Electrical Engineering

Sharif University of Technology, Tehran 2021 - Present

High School Diploma in Mathematics and Physics

2018 - 2021

LANGUAGES

English (Advanced (C1))

Persian (Native)

INTERESTS

Software Development

Artificial Intelligence

Machine Learning

Robotics



CAREER PROFILE

I am a dedicated Electrical Engineering student at Sharif University of Technology with a strong background in software development, especially in Machine learning, Artificial Intelligence, backend and embedded systems. I have over two years of experience in teaching and project execution in programming and electronics. I am eager to further develop my skills in a professional environment that values innovation and teamwork.



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Lead AI and Robotics Instructor

July 2021 - April 2023

Atomic Energy High School

Led the AI and robotics department, focusing on developing and teaching AI and robotics programs for high school students.

IT Specialist

August 2023 - February 2024

Nimaad Cloud Processing, Tehran

Assisted in implementing cloud-based solutions and managed IT infrastructure for optimized performance and security.

Technical Committee Member

May 2022 - Present

IranOpen Robotics Competition

Participated in organizing and evaluating the national robotics competition, focusing on algorithms challenges.



Python for Everybody

- October 2023

Coursera

Young Entrepreneurs Course

- June 2022

Industrial Management Institute

Technical Committee Certification - May 2023

Iran Open

Technical Committee Certification - May 2024

Iran Open

Date and Time in Python - July 2024

365 Data Science

Data Cleaning and Preprocessing with pandas - August 2024

365 Data Science

Human resources comprehensive course - September 2024

Industrial Management Institute



I have been involved in various projects, focusing on backend development, Al systems, and embedded software.

RCSS.ir - A platform for the Iranian RoboCup community

CLSframework - A gRPC/thrift based framework for Soccer Simulation 2D teams

StarterAgent2D-V2 Base - A base code for students in Soccer Simulation 2D teams

PUBLICATIONS

- Pyrus 2023 Team Description Paper Iran Open
- Tehran2D Team Description Paper RoboCup
- Observation Denoising in CYRUS Soccer Simulation 2D Team For RoboCup 2024 RoboCup



Programming Languages

Python, C++, C, CSS, HTML, JavaScript

Data Base
MySQL
Artificial Intelligent Concepts

Machine Learning Frameworks

Deep Learning, Deep Reinforcement Learning

Keras, Tensorflow, Stable Baselines3, Pandas, NumPy

os

Ubuntu, Windows

Technologies and Frameworks

Django, Git, GitLAB, Docker, Robot-Framework, Ansible, Arduino

Integrated development environment (IDE)

PyCharm, CLion, VSCode, QT Creator, R Studio, MATLAB

Designed with • by Xiaoying Riley